<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15"?>
<uc-export clientvers="11.0.0-sprint.20141111.1610+build.2828">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[Package Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE
Package Description: This package contains the actions for AE integration with the Azure system. 

  
This package contains the following actions:
* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.GET_SUBSCRIPTION_INFO
  Action Description: This action is used to fetch Subscription details from Azure system as per the specified Subscription Id. We also need to specify the path to authentication certificate (keystore .jks file) and certificate password in order to connect to Azure system. The Output of this action will be an xml printed in the Job report containing detailed information of the specified Azure Subscription.

* Action name : PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.CHANGE_VM_STATE
 Action description :This action is used to change the virtual machine status (start ,restart ,shutdown and shutdown & deallocate).Difference between shutdown and shutdown deallocate is that latter
will release all the resources acquired by the Virtual machine.This action will return request id which can be further used to query the status of the action.

* Action name : PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.CHECK_REQUEST_STATUS
Action description :This action is used to fetch the status of a previously submitted Azure request based on the request id provided by user. The request status is stored and published in an AE variable. The value of request status will be either Succeeded, InProgress or Failed. This action will fail if user provides an invalid request id which does not exist in Azure system.

* Action name :PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_VM
Action description :This action is used to delete the given virtual machine in the cloud service.The action will return the request id which can be further queried to get the status of VM.
Also if delete attached media is selected YES than it will delete the associated media (operating system disk.data disk and the source blobs) not the container.

* Action name : PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_VM_DEPLOYMENT
Action description :The Create Virtual Machine Deployment Action creates a deployment and then creates a Virtual Machine in the deployment based on the provided xml configuration file and service name. If action executed successfully, it will return request status id that will be used to check status of executed action.

* Action name : PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_STORAGE_CONTAINER
Action description : This action is used to create a Container in the Azure Storage account provided by the user. The Container is created based on the storage account information(account name and access key) and parameters like container name and access type.
The Action will fail when:
* A container with the same name already exists in storage account
* A container with the same name is being deleted at the same time 

* Action name :PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_STORAGE_CONTAINER
Action description :This action is used to delete a Container in the Azure Storage account provided by the user. The Delete Container action marks the specified container for deletion. The container and any blobs contained within it are later deleted during garbage collection.To call this action on a container that has an active lease, specify the lease ID.If no value is provided for lease id when there is an active lease,Delete Container action will return 409 (Conflict).If wrong lease ID is provided or a lease ID is provided for a container that does not have an active lease Delete Container action will return 412 (Precondition failed).

* Action name : PCK.AUTOMIC_AZURE.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_CLOUD_SERVICE
Action description :This action is used to create cloud service in Microsoft Azure asynchronously at specified geographical location by user. This action will return request id which can be further used to query the status of the action.
The Action will fail when:
* If provided cloud service name which is already exist
* If provided cloud service Label is not base-64-encodede]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>
